<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!-- MCM Menu -->
<string_table>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_title">
        <text>Spotters Configuration</text>
    </string>
     <string id="ui_mcm_menu_spotter">
        <text>Spotters</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help0">
        <text>When a squad joins you there is a slim chance that one of its member has the Spotter perk. This stalker will have this perk until he dies, so keep tabs on him</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help0">
        <text>Upon joining you will be notified if a squad member has the Spotter perk with a news notification on your pda</text>
    </string>          
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help1">
        <text>A squad member with the Spotter perk will mark the first enemy he sees whenever he or the squad enters in combat. This is followed by a voice cue (bark) from the squad member</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help2">
        <text>The marker will stays on the enemy, until dispelled by the life timer or when getting too close or too far away from it</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help3">
        <text>When multiple spotting, the next spot is done only after the previous spotted enemy is killed</text>
    </string>      
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_general_help4">
        <text>Hold hotkey (default companion wheel key C) to call new marks. You can change this below</text>
    </string>      
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_hotkey">
        <text>Call Mark hotkey</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_hotkey_desc">
        <text>Hold this key to call a new mark</text>
    </string>    
	<string id="ui_mcm_spotter_perk_chance">
		<text>Perk chance</text>
	</string>    
	<string id="ui_mcm_spotter_perk_chance_desc">
		<text>The chance a squad member that joins you has, to spawn with the Spotter perk</text>
	</string>      
	<string id="ui_mcm_spotter_has_perk">
		<text>The squad member %s has the Spotter perk</text>
	</string>         
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_marker_life">
        <text>Marker life</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_marker_life_desc">
        <text>Time in seconds the marker is shown</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_keep_spotting">
        <text>Keep spotting</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_keep_spotting_desc">
        <text>Your squad will keep spotting after the first enemy. Beware!! You are entering skill issue territory</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_bark">
        <text>NPC Bark</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_spotter_bark_desc">
        <text>The squad member that calls the mark, issues a voice bark as well</text>
    </string>                 
</string_table>